Guide to the John Burroughs Papers, 1850-1991 (bulk 1860-1921)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES IV. CORRESPONDENCE: OUTGOING, 1857-1921
  - To Julian Burroughs
    - Oct 1910, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 14.24)
    - 16 Dec 1910, (1 letters, transcript, annotated) (Folder 14.25)
    - 17 Dec 1910, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 15.1)
    - 2 Jan 1911, (1 letter, transcript, annotated, enclosure) (Folder 15.2)
    - 6-9 Jan 1911, (1 letter, 3 postcards, 3 annotated) (Folder 15.3)
    - 11-20 Jan 1911, (2 letters, 1 postcard, 3 annotated) (Folder 15.4)
    - Feb 1911, (1 letter, 1 postcard, 2 annotated) (Folder 15.5)
    - 5-10 Mar 1911, (2 letters, 2 postcards, 3 annotated) (Folder 15.6)
    - 15-24 Mar 1911, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 15.7)
    - May 1911, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 15.8)
    - 17 June 1911, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 15.9)
    - 27 June 1911, (1 postcard, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.10)
    - 28 June 1911, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.11)
    - 30 June 1911, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 15.12)
    - July-Aug 1911, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 15.13)
    - 26 Aug 1911, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.14)
    - 20 Sep 1911, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.15)
    - 23 Sep 1911, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 15.16)
    - 6 Oct 1911, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 15.17)
    - 11 Oct 1911, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.18)
    - 21 Oct 1911, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.19)
    - 26 Oct 1911, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 15.20)
    - Jan 1912, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 15.21)
    - 7 Feb 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.22)
    - 14 Feb 1912, (1 postcard, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.23)
    - 27 Feb 1912, (1 fragment, transcript, annotated photocopy) (Folder 15.24)
    - 12-14 Mar 1912, (1 letter, 1 postcard, 2 annotated) (Folder 15.25)
    - 19 Mar 1912, (1 postcard, transcript, annotated photocopy) (Folder 15.26)
    - 26 Mar 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.27)
    - 28 Mar 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.28)
    - 4 Apr 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.29)
    - 1 July 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.30)
    - 11 July 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.31)
    - 21 July 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.32)
    - 6 Sep 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.33)
    - 14 Sep 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 15.34)
    - 29 Sep 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.1)
    - 15 Oct 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.2)
    - 12 Nov 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.3)
    - 15 Dec 1912, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.4)
    - 16 May 1913, (1 letter, 2 transcripts, 2 annotated) (Folder 16.5)
    - 19 May 1913, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.6)
    - 22 July 1913, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.7)
    - 5 Aug 1913, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.8)
    - 7 Aug 1913, (1 postcard, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.9)
    - 22 Aug 1913, (1 transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.10)
    - 23 Aug 1913, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.11)
    - 10 Sep 1913, (1 letter, transcript, annotated, 1 enclosure) (Folder 16.12)
    - 13 Sep 1913, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.13)
    - 13-22 Jan 1914, (1 letter, 2 postcards, 3 annotated) (Folder 16.14)
    - 27 Jan 1914, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.15)
    - Feb 1914, (2 letters, 2 postcards, 4 annotated, 1 enclosure) (Folder 16.16)
    - Mar-Apr 1914, (1 letter, 1 postcard, 2 annotated) (Folder 16.17)
    - July 1914, (2 letters, 2 annotated, 1 enclosure) (Folder 16.18)
    - Aug 1914, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 16.19)
    - Sep 1914, (3 letters, 1 postcard, 4 annotated) (Folder 16.20)
    - 8 Dec 1914, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 16.21)
    - 14 Dec 1914, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.22)
    - 25 Dec 1914, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 16.23)
    - Jan-Mar 1915, (3 letters, 2 postcards, 4 annotated) (Folder 16.24)
    - Aug 1915, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 16.25)
    - Sep 1915, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 16.26)
    - 24 Dec 1915, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.27)
    - 31 Dec 1915, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.28)
    - Feb 1916, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 16.29)
    - 4 Mar 1916, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 16.30)
    - 23 July 1916, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 17.1)
    - 11 Aug 1916, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 17.2)
    - 6 Oct 1916, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 17.3)
    - 21 Feb 1917, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 17.4)
    - 2 Mar 1917, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 17.5)
    - 8 Mar 1917, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 17.6)
    - 14 July 1917, (1 letter, photocopy, transcript) (Folder 17.7)
    - 21 July 1917, (1 photocopy, transcript, annotated) (Folder 17.8)
    - 28 July 1917, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 17.9)
    - 5 Aug 1917, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 17.10)
    - 17 Aug 1917, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 17.11)
    - 6 Sep 1917, (1 letter, transcript, annotated) (Folder 17.12)
    - 13 Sep 1917, (1 letter, 2 transcripts, 2 annotated) (Folder 17.13)
    - 19 Feb 1918, (1 letter, photocopy, annotated) (Folder 17.14)
    - Mar 1918, (1 fragment, annotated) (Folder 17.15)
    - July-Aug 1918, (4 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 17.16)
    - Sep 1918, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 17.17)
    - Oct 1918, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 17.18)
    - Dec 1918, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 17.19)
    - To Julian and John (son of Julian) Burroughs, Jan 1919; (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 17.20)
    - To Julian and John (son of Julian) Burroughs, Feb 1919; (2 letters, 1 annotated) (Folder 17.21)
    - Mar-Apr 1919, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 17.22)
    - June 1919, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 17.23)
    - To Julian and Emily Burroughs, July 1919; (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 17.24)
    - Aug 1919, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 17.25)
    - Sep 1919, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 17.26)
    - Oct 1919, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 17.27)
    - Feb-Mar 1920, (2 letters, 1 postcard, 3 annotated) (Folder 18.1)
    - June 1920, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 18.2)
    - 5-13 July 1920, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 18.3)
    - 18-28 July 1920, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 18.4)
    - 6-10 Aug 1920, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 18.5)
    - 11 Aug 1920, (1 photocopy, transcript, annotated) (Folder 18.6)
    - 12-26 Aug 1920, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 18.7)
    - To Julian and John (son of Julian) Burroughs, Sep 1920; (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 18.8)
    - Oct 1920, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 18.9)
    - Nov 1920, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 18.10)
    - Dec 1920, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 18.11)
    - Jan 1921, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 18.12)
  - To Ursula Burroughs
    - Sep 1857- Apr 1858, (6 letters, 6 annotated) (Folder 18.13)
    - July 1858- Jan 1859, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 18.14)
    - Jan-Feb 1859, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 18.15)
    - July 1859- Apr 1860, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 18.16)
    - May 1860- Aug 1861, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 18.17)
    - Oct 1861- July 1862, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 18.18)
    - Sep-Oct 1862, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 18.19)
    - Aug-Nov 1863, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 18.20)
    - Nov-Dec 1863, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 18.21)
    - Dec 1863- Jan 1864, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 18.22)
    - Jan-Feb 1864, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 18.23)
    - Feb-July 1864, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 18.24)
    - July-Aug 1864, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 19.1)
    - Sep 1864- June 1868, (5 letters, 1 envelope, 6 annotated) (Folder 19.2)
    - July 1868- July 1869, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 19.3)
    - June 1870, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 19.4)
    - July-Aug 1870, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 19.5)
    - Aug 1870- June 1871, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 19.6)
    - July-Oct 1871, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 19.7)
    - Oct 1871- Jan 1873, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 19.8)
    - Jan 1873, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 19.9)
    - Jan-Feb 1873, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 19.10)
    - Feb-May 1873, (4 letters, 1 enclosure, 5 annotated) (Folder 19.11)
    - June-July 1873, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 19.12)
    - July-Aug 1873, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 19.13)
    - Dec 1873, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 19.14)
    - Jan 1874, (3 letters, 1 enclosure, 3 annotated) (Folder 19.15)
    - May 1874- July 1876, (6 letters, 6 annotated) (Folder 19.16)
    - Aug 1876, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 19.17)
    - Sep 1876, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 19.18)
    - Oct 1876, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 19.19)
    - July-Aug 1877, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 20.1)
    - Sep 1877- July 1878, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 20.2)
    - Feb 1881, (7 letters, 7 annotated) (Folder 20.3)
    - Mar 1881, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 20.4)
    - Apr 1881- May 1886, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 20.5)
    - June 1887, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 20.6)
    - Sep 1888, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 20.7)
    - July-Aug 1889, (6 letters, 6 annotated) (Folder 20.8)
    - June-Dec 1892, (4 letters, 4 annotated, 1 transcript) (Folder 20.9)
    - May 1899- Dec 1903, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 20.10)
    - Aug 1905, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 20.11)
    - Jan-Feb 1909, (3 letters, 3 annotated, 2 enclosure) (Folder 20.12)
    - Mar 1909, (3 letters, 3 annotated, 1 enclosure) (Folder 20.13)
    - Apr-May 1909, (4 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 20.14)
    - June 1909, (1 letter, 1 annotated, 1 enclosure) (Folder 20.15)
    - Aug 1910- Sep 1912, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 20.16)
    - Feb 1914- Sep 1915, (3 letters, 2 annotated, 1 enclosure) (Folder 20.17)
    - 10 Feb 1916, (1 letter, 1 annotated, 1 enclosure) (Folder 21.1)
    - 12 Feb 1916, (1 letter, 1 annotated, 1 enclosure) (Folder 21.2)
    - 17 Feb 1916, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 21.3)
    - 29 Feb 1916, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 21.4)
    - 8 Mar 1916, (1 letter, 1 annotated, 1 enclosure) (Folder 21.5)
    - 9-13 Mar 1916, (2 letters 2 annotated) (Folder 21.6)
    - 14-19 Mar 1916, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 21.7)
    - 3 Apr 1916, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 21.8)
    - Nov 1916-Feb 1917, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 21.9)
  - To Others
    - To Edna Albert, 1912; (6 letters - transcripts only) (Folder 46.3)
    - To Miss Altchul, 4 Aug [no year]; (1 ALS) (Folder 67.24)
    - To Anni Angell, 10 June 1887; (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 49.23)
    - To Mary Beal, 1909-1916, undated; (7 letters) (Folder 49.24)
    - To Samuel C. Beane, [1910]; (1 letter) (Folder 21.10)
    - To Myron Benton, 1887 or 1888; (1 letter, unfinished and never sent, with EBK's transcription) (Folder 49.22)
    - To Edward W. Bok [editor of Brooklyn Magazine], 1887; (2 letters) (Folder 63.77)
    - To Edward W. Bok [editor of Brooklyn Magazine], 1893; (1 letter, framed) (Box 66 (Oversize))
    - To Leonard Morgan Brown, regarding Walt Whitman, 25 Feb 1885; (1 ALS) (Folder 67.25)
    - To Grace Porter Cleveland, 1908, undated; (photocopies) (Folder 50.3)
    - To Frank Connell, 1914, 1918, undated; (9 letters) (Folder 21.11)
    - To J.E. Christie, 22 March 1906; (1 ALS) (Folder 63.88)
    - To Madeleine Edison, 11 June 1914; (1 ALS) (Folder 63.85)
    - To Mr. and Mrs Foreman, 1914, undated; (2 ALS) (Folder 63.82)
    - To Mr. Gilbert, undated; (1 ALS) (Folder 63.82)
    - To Mr. and Mrs. Richard Watson Gilder, 1878-1905; (8 ALS, 17 p.) (Folder 21.12)
    - To John Gould, 6 Oct 1911; (1 TLS) (Folder 63.84)
    - To Thomas Wentworth Higginson, 1868; (1 letter, ms. copy) (Folder 21.13)
    - To [Thomas Wentworth] Higginson, 17 Jan 1887; (1 ALS) (Folder 63.87)
    - To E. C. Huffaker, 1919; (1 letter, typed, edited draft) (Folder 21.14)
    - To [Clifton] Johnson, 27 March 1881; (1 ALS) (Folder 63.86)
    - To Clifton Johnson, 1897, 1912; (1 letter, 1 photocopy) (Folder 50.1)
    - To Georgia Avery Kendrick, undated; (1 letter) (Folder 21.15)
    - To Hamilton W. Mabie, 1894-1897; [4 ALS] (Folder 51.16)
    - To Mary Newton, 1903, undated; [2 ALS, 1 photograph negative with prints of unidentified woman] (Folder 63.78)
    - To Annie S. Peck, 7 Sep [1919]; (1 ALS) (Folder 67.26)
    - To Clara Stillman Reed, 1899-1913; (9 letters,typed transcripts) (Folder 21.16)
    - To Clara Stillman Reed, 1900-1913; (5 letters, w/ 1 photo of JB at Woodchuck Lodge, described on verso in JB's hand) (Folder 21.17)
    - To Theodore Roosevelt, 9 May 1899; (1 transcript) (Folder 50.8)
    - To Minnie Rouland, 1915-1920, undated; (4 letters, w/ 1 from both Minnie and Orlando and 1 from Duke of Argyl) (Folder 21.18)
    - To Orlando Rouland, 1908, 1910; (2 letters) (Folder 21.19)
    - To Thomas N. Shannon, [1920]; (2 letters, draft replies) (Folder 21.20)
    - To [Edmund Clarence] Stedman, 18 Nov 1883; (1 damaged ALS) (Folder 63.83)
    - To James Monroe Taylor, 1886; (1 letter) (Folder 21.21)
    - To Mary W. Whitney, 1887-1895; (3 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 21.22)
    - To others, 1897-1913; (11 letters, 1 postcard) (Folder 21.23)
    - To others, 1916-1917; (3 letters, typescripts) (Folder 21.24)
    - Autograph cards and notes by JB, 1902-1910, undated; (4 notes, 1 card) (Folder 21.25)
    - To the editor of Recreation, 14 Jan [no year]; (1 letter) (Folder 63.79)
- SERIES V. CORRESPONDENCE: INCOMING, 1850-1928
  - Family: Burroughs, Amelia
    - 1866-1871, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 21.26)
  - Family: Burroughs, "Chant"
    - Jan 1913, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 21.27)
  - Family: Burroughs, Chauncey
    - 1856, (1 letter — facsimile) (Folder 21.28)
    - Nov 1857 - Feb 1858, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 21.29)
    - July 1858 - Mar 1859, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 21.30)
    - May 1860 - Sep 1861, (6 letters, 6 annotated) (Folder 21.31)
    - Mar 1863 - Dec 1863, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 21.32)
    - July -Nov 1864, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.1)
    - Feb-July 1865, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.2)
    - Sep-Nov 1865, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 22.3)
    - Mar-Aug 1866, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 22.4)
    - Aug 1866 - May 1867, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.5)
    - Jan-June 1868, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.6)
    - July 1868 - Oct 1869, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.7)
    - Feb 1870 - Oct 1871, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 22.8)
    - Dec 1871 - Feb 1873, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.9)
    - Mar 1873 - Jan 1875, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 22.10)
    - Mar 1875 - Mar 1876, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.11)
    - Aug 1876 - May 1877, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.12)
    - July 1877 - July 1878, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.13)
    - Oct 1878 - Nov 1880, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 22.14)
    - Dec 1880 - Feb 1882, (3 letters, 2 postcards, 5 annotated) (Folder 22.15)
    - May-Nov 1882, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 22.16)
  - Family: Burroughs, Curtis and Ann
    - 1896-1906, (3 letters, 1 photocopy, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.17)
  - Family: Burroughs, D.M.
    - Mar-Sep 1907, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 22.18)
  - Family: Burroughs, Eden
    - 1885 - Mar 1903, (6 letters, 6 annotated) (Folder 22.19)
    - June 1903 - 1912, (4 letters, 1 postcard, 5 annotated) (Folder 22.20)
  - Family: Burroughs, Hiram
    - 1859 - 1863, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 22.21)
    - 1864 - Apr 1865, (5 letters, 5 annotated) (Folder 22.22)
    - 1866 - Oct 1867, (7 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 22.23)
    - Nov 1867 - Nov 1868, (5 letters, 1 annotated) (Folder 22.24)
    - Dec 1868 - 1869, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 22.25)
    - 1870 -1873, (4 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 22.26)
    - 1874, (6 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 22.27)
    - Jan-Sep 1875, (3 letters, 1 annotated) (Folder 23.1)
    - Nov 1875 - June 1876, (4 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 23.2)
    - June 1877 - Sep 1878, (4 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 23.3)
    - Mar 1880 - Aug 1882, (4 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 23.4)
    - Aug 1882 - 1883, (5 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 23.5)
    - 1884, (2 letters, 1 annotated) (Folder 23.6)
    - 1885 - 1886, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 23.7)
    - 1887 - Oct 1888, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 23.8)
    - 1889 - 1892, (4 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 23.9)
    - Bartram, Uriah — list of letters from JB to HB, 1888 - 1890 (Folder 23.9)
    - 1896 - 1901, (5 letters, 3 postcards, 6 annotated) (Folder 23.10)
    - Jan-Mar 1902, (5 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 23.11)
    - Apr-May 1902, (3 letters, 2 enclosure, 3 annotated) (Folder 23.12)
  - Family: Burroughs, Julian
    - July 1897, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 23.13)
    - Sep 1897, (2 letters, 1 postcard, 2 annotated) (Folder 23.14)
    - Oct 1897, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 23.15)
    - 1-17 Nov 1897, (3 letters, 5 enclosure, 3 annotated) (Folder 23.16)
    - 27 Nov 1897, (1 letter, 1 postcard, 2 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 23.17)
    - Dec 1897, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 23.18)
    - Jan 1898, (4 letters, 1 postcard, 1 enclosure, 5 annotated) (Folder 23.19)
    - Feb 1898, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 23.20)
    - Mar 1898, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 23.21)
    - Apr 1898, (3 letters, 1 enclosure, 3 annotated) (Folder 23.22)
    - May 1898, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 23.23)
    - June 1898, (2 letters, 2 postcards, 1 enclosure, 4 annotated) (Folder 23.24)
    - Sep 1898, (2 postcards, 2 annotated) (Folder 23.25)
    - Oct 1898, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 24.1)
    - Nov 1898, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 24.2)
    - Jan 1899, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 24.3)
    - Feb 1899, (3 letters, 1 enclosure, 3 annotated) (Folder 24.4)
    - 2-7 Mar 1899, (2 letters, 1 postcard, 3 annotated) (Folder 24.5)
    - 12-31 Mar 1899, (3 letters, 1 photocopy, 3 annotated) (Folder 24.6)
    - 1-10 Apr 1899, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 24.7)
    - 11-14 Apr 1899, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 24.8)
    - 1-6 May 1899, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 24.9)
    - 16-21 May 1899, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 24.10)
    - June-July 1899, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 24.11)
    - Sep 1899, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 24.12)
    - Oct 1899, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 24.13)
    - Nov 1899, (3 letters, 1 enclosure, 3 annotated) (Folder 24.14)
    - Dec 1899, (4 letters, 4 annotated, 2 enclosure) (Folder 24.15)
    - Jan 1900, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 24.16)
    - 1-9 Feb 1900, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 24.17)
    - 20-24 Feb 1900, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 24.18)
    - Mar 1900, (4 letters, 4 annotated) (Folder 24.19)
    - Apr 1900, (2 letters, 1 postcard, 3 annotated) (Folder 24.20)
    - May 1900, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 24.21)
    - June 1900, (2 letters, 1 enclosure, 2 annotated) (Folder 25.1)
    - Aug 1900, (1 letter, 1 postcard, 2 annotated) (Folder 25.2)
    - Oct 1900, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 25.3)
    - Dec 1900, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.4)
    - 17-18 Feb 1901, (2 letters 2 annotated) (Folder 25.5)
    - 20 Feb 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.6)
    - 28 Feb 1901, (1 letter, 1 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.7)
    - 1 Mar 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.8)
    - 6-11 Mar 1901, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 25.9)
    - 3 Apr 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.10)
    - 16 Apr 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.11)
    - 25 Apr 1901, (1 letter, photocopy, annotated) (Folder 25.12)
    - 2 May 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.13)
    - 19 May 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.14)
    - 23 May 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.15)
    - 29 May 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.16)
    - June 1901, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 25.17)
    - 19 Sep 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.18)
    - 21 Sep 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.19)
    - 25 Sep 1901, (1 letter,1 annotated) (Folder 25.20)
    - 26 Sep 1901, (1 letter, 1 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.21)
    - 1 Oct 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.22)
    - 4 O ct 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.23)
    - 6 Oct 1901, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.24)
    - 7-10 Oct 1901, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 25.25)
    - Jan 1902, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 25.26)
    - Feb 1902, (1 letter, 2 annotated) (Folder 25.27)
    - 16 Feb 1903, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.28)
    - 17 Feb 1903, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 25.29)
    - Mar 1903, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.1)
    - Apr 1903, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.2)
    - May 1903, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.3)
    - July 1903, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.4)
    - 1 Aug 1903, (1 letter, 1 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.5)
    - 9 Aug 1903, (1 letter, 1 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.6)
    - 12 Aug 1903, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.7)
    - 14 Dec 1903, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.8)
    - 21-26 Dec 1903, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.9)
    - Jan 1904, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.10)
    - Jan-Feb 1905, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 26.11)
    - July 1905, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.12)
    - Feb 1906, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.13)
    - Aug 1906, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.14)
    - Jan 1907, (1 letter, 3 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.15)
    - 9 Feb 1907, (1 letter, 1 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.16)
    - 13 Feb 1907, (1 letter, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.17)
    - Mar 1907, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.18)
    - Apr 1907, (2 letters, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.19)
    - July 1907, (1 letter, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.20)
    - Aug 1907, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 26.21)
    - 19 Sep 1907, (1 letter, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.22)
    - 20 Sep 1907, (1 letter, 1 postcard, 1 enclosure, 2 annotated) (Folder 26.23)
    - Feb 1908, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.24)
    - 3 Feb 1908, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.25)
    - 5 Feb 1908, (1 letter, 2 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.26)
    - 9 Feb 1908, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.27)
    - 22 Feb 1908, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 26.28)
    - 28 Feb 1908, (2 letters, 1 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.1)
    - 8 Mar 1908, (1 letter, 1 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.2)
    - 10 Mar 1908, (2 letters, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.3)
    - 14 Mar 1908, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.4)
    - 22 Mar 1908, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.5)
    - May-June 1908, (1 letter, 1 postcard, 2 annotated) (Folder 54.6)
    - July 1908, (3 letters, 3 annotated) (Folder 54.7)
    - Aug 1908, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.8)
    - Sep 1908, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.9)
    - circa 1909, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.10)
    - Jan 1909, (1 letter, 2 enclosure, 1 photocopy, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.11)
    - Mar 1909, (1 letter, 1 enclosure, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.12)
    - Apr 1909, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 54.13)
    - 9 Oct 1910, (1 letter, 2 annotated, 1 photocopy) (Folder 27.1)
    - 11 Oct 1910, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 27.2)
    - circa 1911, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 27.3)
    - circa Jan 1911, (1 letter, 1 photocopy, 1 annotated) (Folder 27.4)
    - circa Jan 1911, (1 letter, 1 photocopy, 1 annotated) (Folder 27.5)
    - Feb 1911, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 27.6)
    - Mar 1911, (1 letter, 1 photocopy, 1 annotated) (Folder 27.7)
    - May 1911, (1 letter, 1 annotated) (Folder 27.8)